Who are we waiting for?
Dr. Chang.
He said today he'd introduce the elders to
a very important Master-level figure.
That's really nice.
What does he do?
I don't know either.
Anyway, they say he can attract a million fans.
Get famous, break out of the circle.
A million fans, that's good.
But we can't go stepping out of the circle.
He doesn't mean that kind of circle.
That's true.
Here he comes.
Come.
Come, everyone take your seats.
Mr. Liu.
Then I... I'll sit here.
Thank you.
Uncles and Aunties,
esteemed elders,
sorry to keep you waiting.
Today, our retirement community
is very, very honored
to have invited the famous
Mr. Liu Liang.
Alright.
He...
Is he famous?
You don't know Liu Liang?
Never heard of him.
You've heard of him?
I haven't heard of him either.
This Master Liu is
a Master among Masters.
He has previously...
single-handedly...
launched several big internet stars.
Not really.
So today,
we have invited Mr. Liu here
mainly to ask him to
introduce to us...
This... okay.
I'll take it from here.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Thank you for the introduction.
Sure.
And thank you, everyone.
I am Liu Liang.
I came here this time
mainly to share with you Uncles and Aunties
a little bit about
my...
secrets to success.
When it comes to success,
does everyone...
thirst for it or not?
Not thirsty.
I am already a successful person.
Now I'm enjoying my old age.
I've achieved success and retired.
But you can't just lie flat.
Right?
Look at that old guy abroad.
He's nearly ninety.
And he's still serving as president.
That explains why it's a mess over there.
Then look at that old lady abroad.
She's over seventy.
And she can still get pregnant and give birth.
Is that what you're here to teach us?
I'm not here to teach you...
...how to get pregnant and give birth.
I'm here to teach you how to become influencers.
Become influencers?
Don't think it's impossible.
Don't think it's ridiculous.
There's a ninety-three-year-old grandma abroad.
She livestreams eight hours a day.
She has over three million followers.
She's done over a hundred live commerce sessions.
And earned over twenty million.
Compared to them...
...don't you feel...
...a little ashamed?
Not at all.
I just haven't done it.
If I did live commerce...
...I'd have at least twenty million followers.
Then the one feeling ashamed...
...would be that foreign old lady.
If you put it that way...
...the most popular one here...
...should be Mr. Liu.
Isn't that right?
His followers...
...two hundred million.
Don't even compare with Sister Liu.
Let me tell you.
You might not even beat me.
Just based on my time in the matchmaker circle...
...doing good deeds for decades...
...and the popularity I've gathered...
...getting a million followers would be child's play.
So, Mr. Liu...
...let's cut the crap.
Just tell us directly how to do it.
Right.
Okay.
I will now, based on...
...the personal situations of all Uncles and Aunties...
...teach you how to attract millions of fans...
...with the ten top secrets.
Hello, fam.
Today I'm going to perform a piece of...
...Clapper Talk...
..."Raid on the White Tiger Regiment."
If you want a happy and perfect marriage...
...a professional matchmaker must handle it.
Matchmaking for sixty years...
...never missed a shot...
...never made a mistake.
Auntie Cai.
Hold on a second.
This stuff definitely won't work.
Last time, your rhythmic storytelling...
...only got eight likes.
I know other things too!
"Wu Song Fights in the Inn," "Tongrentang."
Well...
Uncle Liang...
...none of those stand a chance.
People these days...
...except for gossip...
...they don't like watching anything.
The first time I played matchmaker was...
How old were you?
Four or five years old.
Huh?
What do you mean "huh"?
That year...
And then the two of them got married.
Isn't this my first time
playing matchmaker?
If you don't believe me,
I have some of Bai Jingjing's
untold secrets.
Spilling big celebrity tea.
That's sure to be popular.
Will this go viral?
For sure.
My daughter, Bai Jingjing,
loved eating white sugar as a kid.
She'd eat plain sugar.
She could eat a whole jar like this.
Like sugar pancakes,
sugar buns,
sugar ears, honey twists, honey cakes...
One time...
Stop it.
This won't work.
Then...
What about her
slacking off on piano as a kid?
I spanked her plenty for that.
Thank you
Thanks for the likes, fam
Just now, I performed "Spring Snow"
So, next up
I will continue by playing another piece for you
"High Mountains and Flowing Water"
Stop
Stop playing, Auntie
Let's not play anymore
What's wrong?
It sounds so good
You're just...
It's either "Spring Snow" or "High Mountains and Flowing Water"
You've been banging away for ages
And only two old geezers are clapping here
This won't do
Who are you calling an old geezer?
No...
Call me Uncle
Uncle
Sit down, Uncle
That won't work either
It's not exciting enough
Then what counts as exciting?
For example
First love
Yes, that works
How old were you?
With whom?
Right
Your daughter is pretty, she must have dated early, right?
Of course
She takes after me in that regard
Can we talk about this?
I think so
A star using her tragic puppy love experience
to educate young people
How do you know it was tragic?
Our Yingzi has experience in this area
I usually
am the one causing tragedy for others
My daughter is the same!
A boy chased her when she was fifteen
He almost committed suicide for her
If not for my timely education
that boy
would have been long gone
So how did you educate her?
I got serious with her right away
I said, having a boy chase you is a good thing
You can't just reject him outright
You have to string him along
No...
Don't let it cost a life
That's how you educated her?
Yeah
Later my daughter got smart
As long as a man chases her
she just dates them for a bit first
Can she still study properly like that?
She wasn't studying that well anyway
Didn't she later
go into singing?
I get it
I didn't become a singing star
mainly because I studied too well
Let me put it this way
Bai Jingjing
the reason she has today's success
and my indulgence of her since childhood
my tolerance and leniency towards her
are inseparable
The reason you guys didn't become singing stars
is not because you studied too well
but because you lacked a
father like me
Hello?
Who is this?
Where did you get this number?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
I don't have a dad.
Are you stupid?
Why do you make me take every call?
There was no caller ID.
They said they're a reporter from City Star News.
No matter who it is.
Cuss them all out for me.
These paparazzi are so annoying.
You have to blame your dad for this.
Why is he ruining you like this?
How many times have I told you?
I don't have a dad.
Will you stop it?
Shameless and pestering me to death.
Auntie.
No.
I... that was a paparazzi just now.
It wasn't directed at you.
Okay, I'll give it to Sister Jingjing right away.
Mom, what is it?
I...
How am I not on your side?
I'm definitely on your side.
I really didn't go see him.
I haven't seen him even once.
As for why he says that...
You go ask him!
Why are you venting your anger on me?
If you keep saying that,
I really will go find him.
He is my biological father, after all.
Enough, stop calling me.
I'm in the middle of filming.
It's gone viral.
The views are approaching 100,000.
Oh my goodness.
Over 98,000.
It's definitely going to break 100,000.
Look at the comments.
Are there any negative ones?
Don't worry, they're all negative.
Is this Bai Jingjing's dad?
Definitely not.
What father would sabotage his daughter like this?
Listen to this one.
Seems it's not just kids who can screw over their dads.
Dads screw over their kids even harder.
And this.
Is Bai Jingjing just collateral damage?
Answer:
No.
This is her dad taking a precision shot.
It counts as a snipe.
Here's a positive comment.
This is so inspiring.
A wayward youth became a pop star.
It lets us underachievers...
see hope.
Does this count as positive?
This one should count as positive, right?
I just like Bai Jingjing.
I like her no matter what you say.
She has a buffoon for a dad.
It's not her fault.
Right.
Here's one debunking the rumor.
You guys actually believe this?
One look and you know this guy isn't Bai Jingjing's dad.
Look at this.
Where does Bai Jingjing look anything like him?
That makes sense.
Uncle Liang and Bai Jingjing's looks...
really aren't alike.
They don't even have the same surname.
Well then.
We've been duped.
Wait...
It's so obvious.
Why didn't any of you notice?
No...
It's just that...
Mainly because we didn't think...
Uncle Liang would lie to us at his age.
We must verify this immediately.
Let's go.
Ver...
Verify.
Coming.
Come on.
So many people here.
You all saw the news online, right?
We did.
Senior Liang.
At your age...
we trusted you so much.
How could you deceive us?
What kind of talk is that?
She really is fifteen.
We didn't ask about that.
Speak.
Is Bai Jingjing really your daughter?
Why is her surname Bai if yours is Liang?
Why do the two of you...
look nothing alike?
About that question...
If I just answer you like this,
it would be a waste.
I suggest...
let's record another video, okay?
Come, set up the lights. Adjust the dimmer.
Set up the camera. Change the background.
Get me a pot of flowers here.
Don't busy yourself just yet.
You should first explain why she's a Bai...
and you're a Liang.
Clear this up for us.
She used to be a Liang.
Later she became a Bai.
Stage name.
Do stage names involve changing surnames?
Back then, darn it...
I... I'm not swearing.
It was darn it...
No...
I'm not swearing.
It's her mother's surname.
Then why did she change to that surname?
Well, that's just because she...
well, her mom and I...
got divorced.
The relationship fell apart.
Sorry about that.
Nothing to be sorry about.
Single-parent families are common now.
My parents are like that.
They divorced when I was ten.
Alright, don't...
don't get sidetracked.
Then why...
does Bai Jingjing look nothing like you?
She...
she used to look exactly like me.
But then, we got divorced.
She went with her mom and...
she changed her looks.
No...
Looks can change too?
Well...
You...
ask them.
Why look at me?
I haven't had plastic surgery anyway.
I...
have natural double eyelids.
I definitely haven't had work done.
Right.
Anyway, let's put it this way.
Right now, only from my face
can you see Bai Jingjing's
childhood charm.
Dear viewers,
dear fam,
behind me is Yangliu Xincheng Retirement Community.
The focus of many netizens,
Mr. Liang, who claims to be Bai Jingjing's father,
is rumored to live right here.
Famous star Bai Jingjing's...
Why isn't he coming out yet?
How about letting us in to find that
Evergreen District, No. 3?
Back.
The person,
our security team has gone to get him.
I believe
he will definitely come out.
Here.
Hello.
May I ask,
you...
why don't you look Chinese?
I am a white Chinese of German ancestry.
Didn't know Bai Jingjing was mixed!
No wonder she's so pretty.
I am not Ms. Bai Jingjing's father.
You aren't?
Then why walk right in the middle?
I am not.
Hello, may I ask if you are...
He is.
So you are!
I'd like to ask...
Friends from the media,
let's not disturb the elders here.
I've prepared a conference room for everyone.
Mr. Liang
will accept interviews in the conference room.
Alright.
Okay.
Fine then.
Come.
Enter in an orderly fashion.
Orderly fashion.
Come, orderly fashion.
Mr. Liang,
ask when we get there.
Mr. Liang, regarding your daughter,
what makes you most proud?
She's smart.
Takes after me.
So Bai Jingjing's
grades were really good growing up?
Either first or second place.
That's amazing!
From the bottom.
May I ask,
regarding raising your star daughter,
what is your secret to success?
You've asked the right person.
Let's not talk about the distant past.
Let's start from
prenatal education.
I remember when Bai Jingjing was still in the womb,
we exposed her to all kinds of music every day.
Like Beethoven, Glinka,
Enicar, Omega...
We played them for her every day.
She listened.
Later, on the day the child was born,
the doctor was scared to death.
She came out bobbing her head.
The doctor asked, "What's going on?"
"What's the situation?"
He said, "This is rock and roll!"
"This is a future rock superstar!"
"Don't you know that?"
Later, as soon as her mom breastfed her,
her head stopped moving.
Papa Liang,
I'd like to ask you,
in raising Bai Jingjing to be a star,
you really took great pains.
But why is it that in every acceptance speech,
Bai Jingjing only mentions her mother,
and never mentions you?
Believe it or not,
I have always been someone who
does good deeds without leaving a name.
Working silently, not asking for rewards.
Keeping the difficulties to myself,
and leaving the honor
to others forever.
In a word,
a modern-day Good Samaritan.
That's the nickname the two of them gave me.
Mr. Liang, let's stop beating around the bush.
Can you tell us directly,
back then, you and your ex-wife,
why did you get divorced?
Mr. Liang,
rumor has it that
you had an affair back then,
and abandoned your wife and daughter,
never returning to their side.
So that to this day,
they still haven't forgiven you.
Where did you hear that?
This is
completely untrue!
Back then,
I did indeed leave them back then.
But later I realized my mistake!
I wanted to return to the family!
But they wouldn't accept it.
I heard that later,
you were dumped by that mistress,
and then you regretted it.
Where are you hearing all this?
You...
Don't believe rumors, don't spread rumors. Don't you understand?
I...
I am a prodigal son returning home.
I realized my errors.
I found my way back.
I endured hardships.
Uh, today's interview ends here.
Mr. Liang didn't rest well last night,
so today he's a bit...
No, I rested very well!
I want to speak!
After all these years,
I have a belly full of grievances!
Do you know that?
Let me speak!
Help Mr. Liang back to Evergreen Residence.
Let's go.
Stop making a scene.
Keep order.
What you did
is just like a Chen Meishi, you know?
I don't know.
Who is Chen Meishi?
It's that guy...
the one who abandoned Qin Lianxiang.
Male scum.
What "male scum"?
I'm classified as a scumbag.
Who's a scumbag?
Don't talk about me.
Didn't you also abandon your wife?
We're different.
I was abandoned by my wife.
Is there evidence?
Evidence?
Maybe.
No.
But...
she went to Germany.
Does this count as proof?
That proves you abandoned her!
She...
She went back to her country heartbroken!
Not back to her country.
She went abroad.
My ex-wife is Chinese.
Chinese?
Yes.
That proves even more that you abandoned her!
She left her homeland for Germany!
No.
She wanted to go to Germany.
I wanted to stay in China.
So...
we broke up.
You're really strange too.
You, a foreigner...
why are you so dead set on
staying in our China?
China is good.
I love China.
Good.
I don't have time for an interview right now.
Jingjing.
Is it really you?
What made you think of calling Dad?
No...
It's not that...
You...
Listen to my explanation.
That was all made up by reporters.
I didn't say it.
You must absolutely...
There's a recording?
The reporters faked that recording.
There's footage of me too?
The reporters faked that footage.
You must not believe it.
Then...
Then what do you want Dad to do?
How about...
Dad...
issues a...
statement?
Or Dad holds a...
press conference?
Or Dad gives himself two big slaps?
You...
Jingjing.
As long as you still acknowledge this dad...
whatever you want me to do...
I'll agree to it all.
You...
Aunties, let's do it again.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four.
Just like that.
That should be enough, right?
It doesn't seem very synchronized yet.
Then how about...
How about we do two more?
Old Liang.
I'm really sorry.
I misunderstood you before.
Misunderstood me about what?
I thought you were always bragging.
I didn't believe the big star Bai Jingjing...
...was really your daughter.
You believe it now, right?
Well, that's partly your fault.
You usually talk way too big.
Three parts truth, seven parts fake.
Full of hot air.
Who? Who is?
In the past...
...I won't blame you since you didn't know.
But now that you know...
...that I am Bai Jingjing's biological father...
...why are you still so rude?
Shake the star's dad's hand first.
So Bai Jingjing really is your daughter?
Then why has she...
...never come to Yangliu Xincheng...
...to visit you?
She...
She's busy.
Being a big star these days is so busy.
Her daily schedule...
...is packed absolutely full.
You could say...
...she gets up in the middle of the night...
...and comes back at sundown.
She's too busy.
But no matter how busy...
...she should make time to see you.
Exactly.
She'll come.
She'll definitely come.
You just watch.
Any day now...
...she'll definitely come.
She should be coming to see me.
Good.
Miss Bai.
May I ask when your next project is?
When do you plan to get married?
When is your next project?